Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: New York Police Department Commissioner, 1990-1992, 42731
  - Subseries B: Articles, 42732
    - "Violent Crime and Community Involvement", 1992; 220033 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - "The Year in Review", 1991; 220034 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Subseries C: Community Policing, 213227
    - 34th Precinct Initiatives, 1992; 220324 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - 72nd Precinct - Model Precinct Program, 1990-1992; 220325 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - 102nd Precinct Profile, 1992; 220326 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - 112 Precinct - Community Policing Precinct Analysis and Problem Solving Strategies, 1992; 220327 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - Analysis of Problems and Conditions in the 83rd Precinct, 1992; 220328 (Box 40, Folder 66)
    - Beat Book: The CPD Newsletter, 1988, 1991; 220329 (Box 40, Folder 67)
    - Blueprint for the Future: Information and Technology for Community Policing into the 21st Century, 1992; 220330 (Box 40, Folder 68)
    - Case Study of Patrol Borough Staten Island, 1991; 220331 (Box 40, Folder 69)
    - "The Challenge Implementation Plan Creation of Information Loops Internal and External Dissemination of Information to Assist in the Implementation of Community Policing", ca. 1991; 220333 (Box 40, Folder 70)
    - Citizen Satisfaction Survey, 1992; 221826 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Civilian Complaint Investigative Bureau Annual Report, 1989; 221827 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Clarifying Roles in the Implementation of Community Policing, 1991; 221828 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Communications Action Plan - Linder Report, 1992; 221829 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Communicating Community Policing, 1991; 221830 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Community Affairs Office, 1990-1992; 223195 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - "Community Justice in New York City" - Aric Press, 1991; 223196 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Community-Oriented Police Officers, 1992; 223197 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Community Patrol Officer Program, 1987; 223198 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Community Patrol Officer Program, 1990; 223199 (Box 41, Folder 10-11)
    - "Community Policing: A Citizen's Guidebook", 1992; 223204 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Community Policing Abstract #1: New York City Police Department, 1991; 223205 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - "Community Policing and the Supervisors of the NYPD" - video script, 1991; 223206 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Community Policing Concept Papers, 1991; 223207 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Community Policing Evaluations, 1993; 223208 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - "Community Policing Grows in Brooklyn: An Inside View of the New York City Police Department's Model Precinct" - Antony Pate and Penny Shtull, 1994; 223209 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Community Policing Guidebook, 1992; 223210 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Community Policing in New York City, 1990-1992; 223211 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Community Policing - Linder and Associates, 1991-1992; 223212 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Community Policing Orientation for Police Executives, 1991; 223213 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Community Policing - Positive News Articles, 1991; 223214 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Community Policing Stories, 1991-1992; 223215 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Community Policing Supervisor's Orientation, 1991; 223216 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Community Responsibility under Community Policing, 1992; 223217 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Computer Aided Dispatch, 1992; 223218 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Consultant Proposal - Community Policing, 1992; 223219 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Crime Control Plan: A Citizen/Police Partnership, ca. 1991; 223220 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Executive Retreat, 1991-08-08; 223221 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Executive Session, 1991-03-27; 223222 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Executive Session, 1991-05-09; 223223 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Executive Session, 1991-05-22; 223224 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Executive Session, 1991-06-12; 223229 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Executive Session, 1991-06-26; 223230 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Executive Session on Policing, 1990-06-14 - 1990-06-16; 223231 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Executive Session on Policing, 1991-02-28 - 1991-03-02; 223232 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Exectuvie Session on Policing, 1991-12-05 - 1991-12-07; 223233 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Executive Session on Policing Transcript, 1990-01-25; 223236 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Executive Session Schedule, 1991; 223237 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Exeuctive Session - Training Implications of Community Policing, 1992; 223238 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Executive Session Conference - Community Policing Implementation - Task Updates, 1992-01-16 - 1992-01-17; 223239 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - Executive Staff Conference - Community Policing Implementation Task Updates, 1992-03 - 1992-04; 227275 (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
    - Executive Staff Conference - Community Policing - Task Update Workbook, 1992-03 - 1992-04; 227276 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - "Evaluating the Effectiveness of the Police Department's Community Policing Program" - presentation, ca. 1991; 227277 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - F.B.I. Community Policing Conference, 1991; 227278 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - "General Introduction to Community Policing" - video script, 1991; 227285 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - "History and Evolution of Structural Community Outreach Programs within the NYPD: An Overview", ca. 1984; 227286 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Implementation of Community Policing: Key Task Responsibilities, ca. 1991; 227287 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Implementing Community Policing - John Linder, ca. 1992; 227288 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Inspections Division Community Policing, 1991; 227289 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - The Institutionalization of Community Policing, 1991; 227290 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Integration of Patrol Services at the Precinct Level, ca. 1991; 227291 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - "Lee Brown and Houston: Neighborhood Policing and the Triumph of Democratic Values" - Malcolm Sparrow, Mark Moore, and David Kennedy, 1990; 227292 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Management of Patrol Borough Commands by Bureau Chiefs, 1991; 227293 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - McKinsey and Company Assessment of Community Policing, 1991-1992; 227294 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - "Measuring Community Policing Effectiveness", 1992; 227295 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - "New York City Police Department Proposal: Development of a Performance Measurement System for Community Policing", 1992; 227296 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Office of the Deputy Commissioner for Community Affairs, ca. 1991; 227297 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Patrol Borough Bronx: Community Policing and Community Organizing Reference Guide, 1991; 227298 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Patrol Borough Bronx: Policy/Clergy Conference, 1991; 227299 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Position Descriptions for Key Roles in Community Policing, 1992; 227300 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Precinct Analysis and Community Policing Plan - 1st Quarter Report, 1992; 227301 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Precinct Analysis and Community Policing Plan: Patrol Boroughs - Manhattan South, Manhattan North, 1991; 227302 (Box 42, Folder 28-29)
    - Problem Solving Strategies for Community Policing: A Practical Guide, ca. 1991; 227303 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Q&A with the Police Commissioner, 1992; 227304 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Safe Streets, Safe City: An Omnibus Criminal Justice Program for the City of New York Summary, 1991; 227305 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Speech by Deputy Commissioner Elsie L. Scott about Community Policing in New York, 1991; 227306 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Vera Institute of Justice, 1990; 227307 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Subseries D: Crown Heights, 213228
    - Crown Heights (Restricted), 1991-1993; 227308 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Crown Heights Lawsuit (Restricted), 1992-1997; 227311 (Box 43, Folder 1-16)
    - Police Foundation - Crown Heights Investigation, 1993; 227579 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - "A Report to the Governor on the Disturbances in Crown Heights: An Assessment of the City's Preparedness and Response to Civil Disorder, Vol. I", 1993; 227580 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - "A Report to the Governor on the Disturbances in Crown Heights: An Assessment of the City's Preparedness and Response to Civil Disorder, Vol. II", 1993; 227581 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Subseries E: Speeches, 213229
    - City Hall Conference Concerning Manpower Assessment, 1990-10-02; 227582 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police - Presidential Inaugural Address, 1990-10-10; 227597 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Black Crime in New York City, 1990; 227598 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Youth, Drugs - General Speech, ca. 1990; 227599 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Press Conference - Shootings, 1991-01-07; 227600 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - J. Raymond Jones Democratic Club, 1991-01-10; 227601 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Management Update, 1991-01-10; 227602 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - First Metropolitan Security Seminar, 1991-01-11; 227603 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Annual Observation of Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1991-01-05; 227604 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Open Town Hall Meeting with Councilman Robert J. Dryfoos, 1991-01-15; 227605 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Remarks for the Swearing-In of the New Deputy Commisioner of Training, 1991-01-15; 227606 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Black Bar Association, 1991-01-17; 227607 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - East Side Chamber of Commerce Dinner, 1991-01-22; 227608 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Remarks for the Swearing-In of the New Assistant Commissioner Criminal Justice Matters, 1991-01-22; 227609 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Undercover Promotions, 1991-01-24; 227610 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - A.A.P.L.E. Seminar, 1991-01-29; 227611 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Award Ceremony for the Police Commissioner's 5k Fitness Run, 1991-01-29; 227612 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Mariners' Temple Baptist Church - "Hour of Power", 1991-02-03; 227637 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - National Governor's Association, 1991-02-04; 227638 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Police Olympic Recognition Ceremony, 1991-02-08; 227640 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Budget Hearing of the Borough Presidents, 1991-02-11; 227641 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Press Conference/Assessment, 1991-02-13; 227642 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Northwest Bronx Community and Clergy Coalition, 1991-02-17; 227643 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - City Council Testimony: Arrest to Arraignment Initiatives, 1991-02-19; 227645 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Manhattan Children's Psychiatric Center, 1991-02-19; 229594 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Manhattan District Attorney's Office, 1991-02-19; 227646 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Emerging Telecommunications Technologies, 1991-02-21; 227647 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Law Enforcement Recognition Week, 1991-02-21; 227648 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Police Foundation Dinner, 1991-02-21; 227649 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Seventh Annual Black Police Officers Awards Dinner, 1991-02-22; 227650 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Ministers Against Crime, 1991-02-23; 227651 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Borough President's Cabinet Meeting, 1991-02-25; 227652 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Manhattan College, 1991-02-25; 227653 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - P.A.C.T. Welcoming Remarks, 1991-02-26; 227654 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Town Hall Meeting, 1991-02-26; 227655 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - University Club Luncheon Ford Foundation, 1991-02-26; 227656 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - 3rd Annual Criminal Justice Award, 1991-02-27; 227657 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - African-American Clergy Council, 1991-02-28; 227658 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Community Board #12 Meeting, 1991-02-28; 228744 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Promotion Ceremony for Uniformed and Civilian Members, 1991-02-28; 228745 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Chinese New Year Ceremony, 1991-03-01; 228746 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - NYPD Holy Name Society Breakfast, 1991-03-03; 228747 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Early Intervention Forum: Support Services War in the Persian Gulf, 1991-03-08; 228748 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Holy Name Society of Brooklyn and Queens, 1991-03-10; 228749 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Preliminary Budget Hearing Testimony, 1991-03-13; 228750 (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Brady Bill Testimony, 1991-03-21; 228751 (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Brooklyn Borough President/Community Board Meeting, 1991-03-21; 228752 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Harvard Club: The Wisemen Dinner, 1991-03-21; 228753 (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Public Safety Hearing: Age Requirement, 1991-03-22; 228754 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Anti-Drug Rally - Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1991-03-25; 228755 (Box 44, Folder 53)
    - Mayor's Midtown Citizens' Committee, 1991-03-25; 228756 (Box 44, Folder 54)
    - Staten Island Chamber of Commerce, 1991-03-25; 228757 (Box 44, Folder 55)
    - Undercover Promotions, 1991-03-25; 228758 (Box 44, Folder 56)
    - 17th Precinct Association and Turtle Bay Association, 1991-03-26; 228759 (Box 44, Folder 57)
    - O.M.B. Noon Hour Seminar, 1991-03-26; 228760 (Box 44, Folder 58)
    - Uniformed Promotions, 1991-03-26; 228761 (Box 44, Folder 59)
    - Financial Executive Institute, 1991-03-27; 228762 (Box 44, Folder 60)
    - 79th St. Block Association, 1991-04-01; 228763 (Box 44, Folder 61)
    - Taping of Police Commissioner's Video, 1991-04-01; 228764 (Box 44, Folder 62)
    - Bronx Hispanic Clergy Organization - Police Clergy Recognition Night, 1991-04-02; 228765 (Box 44, Folder 63)
    - Community Affairs and News Directors of NYC Television and All-News Radio, 1991-04-02; 228766 (Box 44, Folder 64)
    - Centurion Award Ceremony, 1991-04-03; 228767 (Box 44, Folder 65)
    - Westside Community Conference, 1991-04-06; 228768 (Box 44, Folder 66)
    - Vanderveer Park United Methodist Church, 1991-04-07; 228769 (Box 44, Folder 67)
    - Police Academy Graduation, 1991-04-09; 228770 (Box 44, Folder 68)
    - 34th Annual NY Emmy Awards, 1991-04-10; 228771 (Box 44, Folder 69)
    - "Women in Policing" Conference, 1991-04-10; 229604 (Box 44, Folder 70)
    - New York State Law Enforcement Council, 1991-04-11; 228772 (Box 44, Folder 71)
    - Police Commissioner's Video Update, 1991-04-11; 228773 (Box 44, Folder 72)
    - Police Retirement Ceremony, 1991-04-12; 228774 (Box 44, Folder 73)
    - Citizens Crime Commission, 1991-04-15; 228775 (Box 44, Folder 74)
    - Cop of the Month, 1991-04-16; 228776 (Box 44, Folder 75)
    - Bronx Shepherd's Resoration Corporation, 1991-04-18; 228777 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - Dowtown-Lower Manhattan Association, 1991-04-18; 228778 (Box 44, Folder 77)
    - Crime Victim's Vigil, 1991-04-21; 228779 (Box 44, Folder 78)
    - Cop of the Month, 1991-04-22; 228780 (Box 44, Folder 79)
    - First Baptist Church - Crown Heights, 1991-05-05; 228781 (Box 44, Folder 80)
    - P.A.C.T. Meeting, 1991-05-06; 228782 (Box 44, Folder 81)
    - NOBLE Hate Crime Videotape, 1991-05-07; 228783 (Box 44, Folder 82)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Association Award Ceremony, 1991-05-10; 228784 (Box 44, Folder 83)
    - Centennial Synagogue, 1991-05-13; 228785 (Box 44, Folder 84)
    - NYC Council Committee on Public Safety: Hearings on Proposal Local Law, Concerning Monthly Reporting of 911 Data, 1991-05-13; 228786 (Box 44, Folder 85)
    - NYC Council Committee on State and Federal Legislation Hearings on Home Rule Message for State Senate Bill 2554: Lateral Transfer of Personnel among Police Agencies Testimony, 1991-05-13; 228787 (Box 44, Folder 86)
    - Police Foundation Award Ceremony, 1991-05-13; 228788 (Box 44, Folder 87)
    - Long Island University Press Conference, 1991-05-14; 228789 (Box 44, Folder 88)
    - National Arts Club Dinner Honoring Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn, 1991-05-14; 228790 (Box 44, Folder 89)
    - 72nd Precinct Public Forum, 1991-05-16; 228791 (Box 44, Folder 90)
    - Community Representatives and the Civilian Compliant Review Board, 1991-05-16; 228792 (Box 44, Folder 91)
    - Peace Officers Memorial Day, 1991-05-17; 228793 (Box 44, Folder 92)
    - Shomrim Society Dinner, 1991-05-17; 228794 (Box 44, Folder 93)
    - St. Paul Community Church's Annual Men's Day, 1991-05-19; 228795 (Box 44, Folder 94)
    - Cop of the Month, 1991-05-20; 228796 (Box 44, Folder 95)
    - NYC Council Budget Hearings - Joint Committee on Finance and Public Safety, 1991-05-21; 228797 (Box 44, Folder 96)
    - Police Surgeon's Dinner, 1991-05-21; 228798 (Box 44, Folder 97)
    - Bensonhurst/Gravesend Town Hall Meeting, 1991-05-23; 228799 (Box 44, Folder 98)
    - Civilian Employees Ceremony, 1991-05-24; 228800 (Box 44, Folder 99)
    - Helicopter Heroism Award, 1991-05-28; 228801 (Box 44, Folder 100)
    - Plum Sock Fund Awards Ceremony, 1991-05-28; 228802 (Box 44, Folder 101)
    - Undercover Promotion Ceremony, 1991-05-30; 228803 (Box 44, Folder 102)
    - Uniformed and Civilian Promotion Ceremony, 1991-05-31; 228804 (Box 44, Folder 103)
    - Conference on Policing in New South Africa, 1991-06-05; 228805 (Box 44, Folder 104)
    - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Awards Ceremony, 1991-06-11; 228806 (Box 44, Folder 105)
    - Building Owners' and Managers' Association Luncheon, 1991-06-12; 228807 (Box 44, Folder 106)
    - Italo-American Associations Dinner, 1991-06-13; 228808 (Box 44, Folder 107)
    - 2nd Annual Conference on Drug Policies, 1991-06-17; 228809 (Box 44, Folder 108)
    - Press Conference - Brady Bill, 1991-06-17; 228810 (Box 44, Folder 109)
    - Long Island City Development Corporation Breakfast, 1991-06-18; 228811 (Box 44, Folder 110)
    - Medal Day, 1991-06-18; 228812 (Box 44, Folder 111)
    - Manhattan Borough Board Meeting: The Civilian Complaint Review Board, 1991-06-20; 228813 (Box 44, Folder 112)
    - New York Community Trust, 1991-06-20; 228814 (Box 44, Folder 113)
    - Gladstone Atwell Intermediate School Graduation, 1991-06-21; 228815 (Box 44, Folder 114)
    - Press Conference: Civil Enforcement 52nd Precinct - Padlocked Apartments, 1991-06-22; 229959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan District United Methodist Men's Communion Breakfast, 1991-06-23; 229960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - F.I.V.E. Star Plan, 1991-06-24; 229961 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Precinct Community Council Presidents, 1991-06-25; 229962 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - NYC Council Committee on Public Safety - Assault Rifles Testimony, 1991-06-26; 229963 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Cop of the Month, 1991-06-27; 229964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Uniform and Civilian Promotion Ceremony, 1991-06-28; 229965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Press Conference: Federal Forfeiture Funds, 1991-07-02; 229966 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Press Conference: I.B.E.W. Observation's Patrol, 1991-07-02; 229967 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Indictment of Alejandro Henriquez, 1991-07-02; 229968 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Riverside Church - "Partnership of Faith", 1991-07-03; 229969 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Corporation Counsel Summer Interns Seminar, 1991-07-05; 229970 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Selected Crime Issues: Prevention and Punishment, 1991-07-10; 229971 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Diamond Center Booth Dedication, 1991-07-15; 229972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Civilian Commendation Ceremony, 1991-07-17; 229973 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Clergy United for Action - "Great Parade Against Drugs", 1991-07-20; 229974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Press Conference: Violence Against Children, 1991-07-22; 229975 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Dedication Ceremony for Detectives Richard J. Guerzan and Keith Williams, 1991-07-24; 229976 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Undercover Promotions Ceremony, 1991-07-25; 229977 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Uniformed and Civilian Promotions Ceremony, 1991-07-25; 229993 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Child's Memorial Temple - Church of God in Christ, 1991-08-04; 229997 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - "Operation YES": Anti-Drug Program, 1991-08-11; 229998 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - City Agenices Involvement in Observation Patrol, 1991-08-14; 229999 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Washington Heights Community Meeting, 1991-085-15; 230000 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Promotions Ceremony, 1991-08-19; 230001 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Promotions Ceremony, 1991-08-23; 230002 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - The United Way of Tri-State, 1991-09-04; 230003 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Juniper Park Civic Association, 1991-09-05; 230004 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Assistant Corporation Counsel Attorneys, 1991-09-06; 230005 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Neighborhood Resource Centers Press Conference, 1991-09-10; 230006 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - 9-1-1 Ceremony Awards, 1991-09-11; 230007 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Retirement Dinner for Charlie Connolly, 1991-09-11; 230008 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - P.A.C.T. Meeting with Foreign Press, 1991-09-19; 230009 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Federal Executive Board, 1991-09-24; 230010 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - 5th Precinct Auxilliary Police Inspection Ceremony, 1991-09-25; 230011 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - National Commission to Study the Cause of the Demand for Drugs in the U.S., 1991-09-25; 230012 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - U.S. House of Representatives Subcommittee on Legislation and National Security Testimony, 1991-09-25; 230024 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Citicorp Private Banking Luncheon, 1991-09-26; 230025 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Citizen of the Month, 1991-09-26; 230026 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Society of Professional Investigators, 1991-09-26; 230027 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Undercover Promotions, 1991-09-26; 230028 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - United Way of New York City - Annual Board of Directors Meeting, 1991-09-26; 230029 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Police Clerical Ball, 1991-09-28; 230030 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - "The Beat Cop Is Back" Press Conference, 1991-10-01; 230031 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - New York University Seminar on Community Policing, 1991-10-01; 230032 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Cop of the Month, 1991-10-02; 230033 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Third Annual Ecumenical Prayer Service, 1991-10-02; 230034 (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 1991-10-08; 230035 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - St. George Association, 1991-10-13; 230036 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - St. Stephern's United Methodist Church, 1991-10-13; 230037 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Assault Weapons Ban Press Conference, 1991-10-14; 230038 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - 9-1-1 Testimony, 1991-10-16; 230039 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - Agudath Israel Conference, 1991-10-16; 230040 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - FBI Conference on Violent Crime and Community Involvement, 1991-10-16; 230041 (Box 45, Folder 54)
    - 71st Precinct Community Council, 1991-10-17; 230042 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - "Leave the Guns at Home" Press Conference, 1991-10-17; 230043 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - Detective's Endowment Association Dinner Dance, 1991-10-18; 230044 (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - City Club of New York Luncheon, 1991-10-19; 230045 (Box 45, Folder 58)
    - Northeast Queens Jewish Community Council, 1991-10-20; 230046 (Box 45, Folder 59)
    - Fund for the City of New York, 1991-10-24; 230047 (Box 45, Folder 60)
    - Women's City Club, 1991-10-24; 230048 (Box 45, Folder 61)
    - Community Policing for Police Executives, 1991-10-25; 230049 (Box 45, Folder 62)
    - Hispanic National Law Enforcement Association, 1991-10-25; 230050 (Box 45, Folder 63)
    - Undercover Promotions, 1991-10-25; 230052 (Box 45, Folder 64)
    - Uniform Promotional Ceremony, 1991-10-25; 230054 (Box 45, Folder 65)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Church of the Resurrection, 1991-10-27; 230056 (Box 45, Folder 66)
    - Asian-American Advisory Council, 1991-10-28; 230058 (Box 45, Folder 67)
    - Police Foundation's Suicide Film Screening, 1991-10-28; 230059 (Box 45, Folder 68)
    - Police Academy Graduation, 1991-10-29; 230062 (Box 45, Folder 69)
    - Citizen of the Month, 1991-10-30; 230064 (Box 45, Folder 70)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Awards Ceremony, 1991-10-30; 230066 (Box 45, Folder 71)
    - 1st Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, 1991-10-31; 230068 (Box 45, Folder 72)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for the New 107th Precinct, 1991-10-31; 230072 (Box 45, Folder 73)